<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DELIGHTFUL</title>
    <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DELIGHTFUL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adimoonshots.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alice</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/alice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/alice/</guid>
      <description>Alice you are an incredible person to hang out with. I hope we can do amazing things together in ADI and that we become closer. Keep going with that smile and energy!
Your confidence and brightness brings out the same in others. You&amp;rsquo;re just really cool :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amy</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/amy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/amy/</guid>
      <description>Amy! You are such a cutie! &amp;lt;3 I love your energy and I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll get to bring a smile to other committee members like you did to me. :)
You are incredibly fun, smart, and it makes me so proud to be your fellow Barnard ADI sister! Much love!
BARNARD BABEEE!!!! I love you sooo much! Seeing you makes my heart warm and I literally am so happy you&amp;rsquo;re a part of our family!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/chris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/chris/</guid>
      <description>CHRIS! Although I&amp;rsquo;ve only known you for a really short time, you are HILARIOUS. Don&amp;rsquo;t let your eccentric die. Thanks for cheering me on when we played hannabi although we all lost because of me :( hope you have an amazing break!
You seem to be someone who is incredibly thoughtful and enjoys meeting people, and making those around you happy. You are a true joy!
Hi Chris! You&amp;rsquo;re such a positive person to be around and full of ideas about how to improve the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erinn</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/erinn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/erinn/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re genuinely caring and an awesome person. I hope to get to know you better throughout the years and that we can work togwther for ADI! (Also, I will remember that you are a sophomore, not a freshman, I promise :)
Your resourcefulness and joy are a true inspiration to me! Sometimes you&amp;rsquo;ll randomly message me and my day gets 101013134234x&amp;rsquo;s better
Erinn! We don&amp;rsquo;t have an official sunshine chair but with you joining us we might as well - thank you for spreading sunshine and happiness everywhere you go, ADI included</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iliana</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/iliana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/iliana/</guid>
      <description>WOW! YOU! ARE! MY! LOVE! You are sooo funny and smart and driven and passionate and caring and silly and thoughtful and just as chingona as they come. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for the things you will do for the community, your passion for BME and CS is so inspiring. Yay Texas! I am so happy you&amp;rsquo;re a part of our family &amp;lt;3
Iliana! You are intellectually curious and it has been an absolute joy to see you learn more with enthusiasm this semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/isaiah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/isaiah/</guid>
      <description>Hey!! glad to have you onboard and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to hanging out
I loved getting to know you during cookies &amp;amp; code and can&amp;rsquo;t wait to do great things with you! You are so funny and I love your style! hyped for the rest of the year :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/james/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/james/</guid>
      <description>I love you! You&amp;rsquo;re my new financial advisor, you have such interesting and random thoughts that make me smile. You are a better version of Neil and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see the great things you&amp;rsquo;ll get done! I have learned so much from you already and am so happy that you&amp;rsquo;re a part of our family!
You have such a funny and likable personality. Excited to work with you this year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kendal</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/kendal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/kendal/</guid>
      <description>I have had incredible conversations with you and can&amp;rsquo;t wait for the many more to come! You have single-handedly have changed cookies &amp;amp; code and can&amp;rsquo;t wait for what more you can do for our community. I loveee your shirts and the fact that you&amp;rsquo;re from Arkansas (no coast is the best coast!) &amp;lt;3
Hi Kendal! You&amp;rsquo;re so positive and an absolute joy to talk to - you really put in the effort to include others in conversation and its a great feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lalitha</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/lalitha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/lalitha/</guid>
      <description>You are sooo cute! And soooo smart! Wow I&amp;rsquo;m so hyped to get to know you!
We&amp;rsquo;re super excited to have you on board with us Lalitha! I&amp;rsquo;m so down to work on inclusivity+DevFest with you.
Thanks for coming to Academi Lalitha! Maybe you can help us run it next semester :)
I was so happy that you discussed the power of technology in education and unprivileged communities with us. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an awesome year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/will/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/will/</guid>
      <description>Will you are one of the funniest people I’ve met. Keep up your great energy and I hope you do freat things for ADI this year!
Will!! Looking forward to teaching you how to use Illustrator :P I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;d be one of my best disciples haha. Have an amazing break!
Excited about how ready you are to start new ADI initiatives even in your second semester senior year!
Will! I&amp;rsquo;ve been completely amazed by how you&amp;rsquo;ve hit the ground running in ADI and how active you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yefri</title>
      <link>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/yefri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adimoonshots.github.io/moonshots/yefri/</guid>
      <description>From the conversations that we&amp;rsquo;ve had, you seem to be someone who really cares about the people around you and your family. Your enthusiasm and excitement to learn and grow in this community are amazing!
I am so excited to have you be a part of our family! Your excitement and drive has been contagious in the short time you&amp;rsquo;ve been here and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for more of it. Your presence in c&amp;amp;c and anything you attend is a great addition :) You have so much to teach us and I hope we can help you help people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>